So what happened? Did a forest tick you off?
怎么回事，森林惹到你了？
We always say we need a place for the mail.
我们一直说需要信件柜
I started building one. But then I decided to take it to the next step.
所以我就动工了，然后呢 我决定更进上一层楼
You're building a post office?
你要盖邮局？
No,an entertainment unit, with a built-in mail cubby.
不是，是一个娱乐专用柜 内含信件柜
It's a one-day job,max.
顶多一天就能搞定 好
My word,those are snug!
你的裤子还真帖啊
These are my old work pants.
这是我的旧工作裤
Sergio Valente.
“亚曼范伦铁”
Power saw kind of got away from me there.
刚才电锯有点失控
The One With Frank Jr.
本集播出：“亲亲小弟”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
Hey,Pheebs. Any sign of your brother?
菲比，你弟出现了吗？
No,but he's always late.
还没，不过他很爱迟到
-I thought you only met him once. -I did.
你不是只见过他一次？ 是啊
I think it sounds big sister-y, "Frank's always late."
这样讲有姐姐的派头 “法兰克老是迟到”
Well,relax. He'll be here.
别急，他会来的
I know. I'm just nervous.
我知道，我只是很紧张
It's just,Mom's dead, don't talk to my sister...
我妈死了，我不和我姐说话
...Grandma's been sleeping a lot lately.
奶奶最近都在睡觉
It's just the "last-desperate- chance-to-have-a-family" kind of thing.
这是我拥有家人的最后机会
You're sweet to wait with me.
你真好，还陪我等
Actually,Gunther sent me. You're not allowed to have cups out here.
是阿甘叫我来的 杯子不能拿出来
Does anyone else think David Copperfield's cute?
还有谁觉得大卫考柏菲可爱？
No. But he told me he thinks you're a fox.
没有，不过他告诉我 他觉得你很帅
All right. Janice likes him.
珍妮丝喜欢他
In fact,she likes him so much, she put him on her "freebie" list.
喜欢到把他放进 她的名人性爱名单里
Her what?
她的什么？
We have a deal where we each pick five celebrities we could sleep with...
我们说好 一人可以挑五个名人上床
...and the other one can't get mad.
另一个人不准生气
The heart of every healthy relationship:
这是健全男女关系的要素
Honesty,respect and sex with celebrities.
诚实、尊重、与名人上床
So who's on your list?
你的名单有谁？
IKim Basinger...
金贝辛格
... Cindy Crawford,Halle Berry...
辛蒂克劳馥、荷莉贝瑞
...Yasmine Bleeth...
雅丝敏布丽丝
...and Jessica Rabbit.
和罗杰兔的老婆洁西卡
You do realize that she is a cartoon, and way out of your league?
你知道她是卡通人物 而且和你不同挂吧？
I know. I just wonder if I could get her eyes to pop out of her head.
我知道，我是看看 我能不能让她的眼珠掉出来
Who would yours be?
摩妮卡，你会选谁？
First,I need a boyfriend. Then I can have a list.
我得先交男朋友，才能列名单
It's just a game,Mon.
只是好玩嘛，妈
Rach,how about you?
瑞秋，你呢？
I don't know. I guess Chris O'Donnell,John F. IKennedy Jr...
不晓得，应该是克里斯欧唐纳 小约翰肯尼迪
... Daniel Day-Lewis,Sting and Parker Stevenson.
丹尼尔戴路易斯、史汀 和帕克史蒂文生
Spiderman?
蜘蛛人？
Hardy Boy.
哈第兄弟神探
-Peter Parker. -Thank you.
是彼得帕克 谢谢（其实瑞秋才是对的）
What about you,honey? Who'd be on your list?
你呢？你会选谁？
That kind of thing requires some serious thought.
这种事需要深思熟虑
First,I'd divide my prospective candidates into categories.
我会先把可能人选分门别类
What a geek!
怪人
Everybody,this is Frank! My half brother,Frank!
各位，这是法兰克 我同父异母的弟弟
This is everybody.
就是他们
-This is Ross. -How are you?
这是罗斯 你好吗？
This is Monica.
这是摩妮卡
And this is Rachel.
这是瑞秋
I'm gonna get coffee for us.
我去点咖啡
Hey,how do you guys get anything done?
你们怎么做得了事？
We don't,really.
我们是没做什么事
Do you guys have big plans?
你们有什么计划吗？
Oh,yeah. We're gonna connect and bond and everything.
有，我们要好好的联络感情
I thought we could go down to Times Square and pick up some ninja stars.
我们会去时代广场 买几个忍者娃娃
My friend,Larry,he wants me to take a picture of a hooker.
我朋友赖瑞托我拍妓女的照片
We really don't take advantage of living in the city.
我们在纽约都白住了
Oh,sorry. Did I get you?
抱歉，我钻到你了？
No,you didn't "get" me!
没有，你没有钻到我
It's an electric drill!
那是电钻
You "get" me,you kill me!
你要是钻到我，我就死了
Calm down! Do you want this unit or not?
别激动 你要不要这个柜子嘛？
I do not want this unit!
我不要这个柜子
You should've told me before. I'm not a mind reader.
你不早说，我又不会心电感应
And we're out of beer. I'm going to Monica's.
没有啤酒了，我要去对面
Fine!
你去啊
Where you heading in those pants? 1982?
你穿这样要去哪里？ 1982年？
I saw down at the hardware store,they got those designer tiles on sale...
对了，我在装潢建材店 看到名牌瓷砖在特价
...if you wanna redo your bathroom floor.
你可以重铺浴室地板
What's wrong with my bathroom floor?
我的浴室地板怎么了？
Nothing. It's just old and dingy, that's all.
没什么，只是又旧又暗
I highly doubt that.
没有这回事
If you move your hamper...
你把篮子移开…
...you see how the tile used to be.
就能看到瓷砖原来的颜色
I can't live like this! What are we gonna do?
这样我怎么住！怎么办？
Relax. Here,hold this.
别激动，拿着
This old stuff comes right up. I'll show you.
瓷砖一撬就掉，我弄给你看
A little more than I wanted to see.
我没想到你要撬它
Look at that! Every inch of this is glued down!
你看看，黏得多死啊
It'd take forever to pry this up. You should just leave it.
撬也撬不完，我看你别管了
I can't leave it! You gouged a hole in my dingy floor!
怎么能不管 你在我的旧地板上撬了个洞
There. There you go.
这样就好了
Yeah,that's nice.
挺好的
We can put it back there after the surgeons remove it from your colon!
塞进你的屁股里会更好
I know what I wanted to ask you. Can you roll your tongue?
我知道我要问什么了 你会卷舌头吗？
Because I can and my mom couldn't.
因为我会，但是我妈不会
And I figured that was something I got from our dad.
我想那一定是爸的遗传
Well,wait,you mean like this?
等一下，你是说这样？
Yeah,you can do it too. Yeah.
对，你也会
You're not doing it.
你没有卷啊
Oh,right. Okay. Yeah,my mom could and I can't.
好吧 所以是我妈会，我不会
We don't have that.
我们这一点不一样
When's your birthday?
你的生日是哪一天？
February 16th.
2月16日
I know a guy who's the 18th.
我认识一个18日的人
That's close.
蛮近的
When's yours?
你的生日呢？
October 25th.
10月25日
That's the same month as Halloween.
跟万圣节同一个月
So what kind of things do you like to do at home?
你在家里喜欢做什么？
Melt stuff.
烧东西
-Okay,I've got three of my five. -Three of your five what?
好，我已经挑了三个 三个什么？
Celebrities I'm allowed to sleep with.
可以上床的名人
God,you're giving this a lot of thought.
天哪，你还真慎重
Hey,it's hard,okay? I only have two spots left.
很难挑好吗？我只剩两个空缺
All right. Who you got it narrowed down to?
你筛选出谁了？
Elizabeth Hurley.
伊丽莎白赫莉
Very attractive.
大美女
Forgiving.
心胸宽大
Susan Sarandon.
苏珊莎兰登
You know what? She's too political.
她太热衷政治了
She'd probably make you donate four cans of food first.
她可能会叫你先捐四个罐头
And lsabella Rossellini.
还有伊莎贝拉罗塞里尼
Very hot. Very sexy.
很辣、很性感
But she's too international. She's never gonna be around.
但是太国际化了 她不会跑来美国的
-So? -So you gotta play the odds.
所以呢？ 所以你得掌握胜算
Pick somebody who's gonna be in the country all the time.
挑一个会一直在国内的人
Yeah. Because that's why you won't get lsabella Rossellini. Geography.
对啊，你之所以钓不到她 是地理因素
Okay. So by "melting" you meant melting.
你说的“烧”就是烧
So is it,like,art?
这是艺术吗？
Yeah,you can melt art.
要烧艺术也可以
Hey,can I use your phone?
可以借个电话吗？
-Sure. You want to call your mom? -No,I want to melt it.
当然，你要打给你妈？ 不是，我想拿来烧
Oh. Well,not right now.
现在不行
I'm gonna go to bed. The fumes are giving me a headache. So....
我要去睡了，烟熏得我头痛
Good night,"bro."
晚安，老弟
Good night.
晚安
Here.
拿去
Just in case.
以防万一
Oh,excellent!
太好了
-What kind of karate is that? -No kind.
那是什么空手道？ 什么都不是
He just makes it up.
那是他自创的
-How's it going with you guys? -So far it kind of blows.
你们处得怎样？ 蛮烂的
I don't know,I just thought he'd feel more like a brother.
我以为他会更有兄弟的感觉
Like you and Ross. Close and connected and....
就像你和罗斯，亲密融洽
We're close now. You wouldn't believe the years...
现在是很亲，但是以前
...of noogies,and wedgies,and flying wedgies,and atomic wedgies and....
我们又吵又打，又拉又扯
That's when the waistband goes over your head.
然后裙子就会被扯到头上来
We drove each other crazy playing the shadow game.
我们还学舌去烦对方
-How do you play the shadow game? -How do you play the shadow game?
什么是学舌？ 什么是学舌？
-I just asked you. -I just asked you.
我在问你啊 我在问你啊
I don't have time for this.
我没空跟你闹
-That is what the game is. -You just gave up really quickly.
这就是学舌 你放弃得真快
-Seen Joey? -What's the matter?
有看到乔伊吗？ 怎么了？
Oh,just this!
就是这个
It's my fault,really,because the couch is where we keep the varnish.
其实是我不好 沙发就是用来放亮光漆的
Somebody wanna hand me one of those tiles?
把瓷砖拿给我
-What's going on? -He's retiling my floor.
怎么回事？ 他在帮我重铺地板
Spackle boy!
泥水匠
-Get up! -You started this,you'll finish it!
给我起来 你要有始有终
He started mine first!
是我先受害的
Build the unit,Cinderellie Lay the tile,Cinderellie
灰姑娘，去钉柜子 灰姑娘，去铺瓷砖
Big octopus.
大章鱼
Oh,my God! I totally forgot!
天哪，我都忘了
Well,can't someone else do it?
不能找别人吗？
But I have company.
但是我有客人
Look,that's all right. I'll come in.
没关系，我去
I'm sorry, but I have to go into work.
对不起，我得去工作
It's one of my regulars who's insisting that I do him,so....
我的一个熟客坚持要让我做
Hey,what kind of work do you do?
你在做什么工作？
I'm a masseuse.
我是按摩师
I give people massages and stuff.
我帮客人按摩
You work at one of those massage parlors?
你在按摩院工作？
Well,you know,we don't call it that. But,yeah.
我们不那样叫，不过没错
That's wild.
好劲爆
No,I had no idea.
我完全不知道
Alrighty.
好吧
I'll be back in a little bit.
我过一会儿就回来
Unless you want to come with me.
除非你想跟我去
You mean,like,watch?
你是说去看吗？
No. No,you can get one yourself. It'll be on the house.
不是，你也可以接受服务 而且是免费招待
What are big sisters for?
不然要姐姐干什么？
Well,I don't think this. You know?
我并没有这么想
No. No,no. I wouldn't do you myself.
不…我不会亲自招呼你
I mean,that would be weird.
那样很奇怪
I'll get one of the other girls to do it.
我会请其他小姐来做 我帮客人按摩
This is so much fun!
真好玩
Are you excited?
你兴奋吗？ 兴奋
Hey,do Monica and Rachel work there?
摩妮卡和瑞秋 也在那里工作吗？
It's beautiful!
好漂亮
It's like the first bathroom floor there ever was!
之前的地板好像一场梦
What are you going in there for?
你想进去干什么？
You want,like,a number?
嘘嘘如何？
Hi. Bye.
再见
Okay. I'm done with my choices.
好，我选好了
These are final.
这是最后名单
-Well,it's about time. -Yeah. Very official.
你也该选好了 对啊，好正式
Oh,yeah. Well,you know,Chandler printed it up on his computer.
对，这是钱德用他的电脑印的
And who laminated it?
谁拿去护贝的？
That was me.
是我
All right,let me see.
拿来我看看
"Uma Thurman,Winona Ryder, Elizabeth Hurley...
乌玛舒曼、薇诺娜瑞德 伊莉莎白赫莉
... Michelle Pfeiffer...
蜜雪儿菲佛
... Dorothy Hamill"?
桃乐丝汉弥尔？（溜冰名将）
Hey,it's my list!
这是我的名单
You do realize she only spins like that on ice?
你知道她只有在冰上 才会一直转吧？
“舒活之家”
-What's going on? -She broke my arm!
怎么了？ 她扭断了我的手
-He touched my fanny. -She touched mine first!
他摸我的屁股 是她先摸我的
That's my job!
那是我的工作
So what's the deal? I can have sex with you but I can't touch you?
什么意思？ 我可以上你，却不能摸你？
-You can't have sex with her! -Did you think I was a hooker?
你不能上她 你以为我是妓女？
No,okay. I know. You're a masseuse. It's cool. I'm not a cop!
不，我知道你是按摩师 很好，我又不是警察
Ask Mr. Wiffler if he can wait for five minutes.
你去请威佛先生等5分钟
Fine.
好
I don't like you.
我不喜欢你
So that's what you thought I did? God!
你以为我是干那行的？天哪！
That's not what I do!
我不是干那行的
Wait,that's not what you do?
你不是干那行的？
No!
不是
Why would you think that?
你怎么会这么想？
I don't know. This is the city, you know? I just....
不知道，这里是纽约嘛
I mean...
我是说…
... I don't know.
我不知道
Whatever. It's the perfect end to the perfect weekend anyway.
随便，好一个完美的周末 完美的句点
Oh,wait.
等一下
No,you're right. No,it was perfect.
你说得没错，真的很完美
I can't believe I screwed it up so bad.
我居然把它搞砸了
You thought it was perfect?
你觉得很完美？
Well,no,maybe it wasn't perfect...
也许称不上完美
... but you know,it was pretty cool, you know?
但还是很酷
Because we had all those great talks,you know?
我们聊得那么愉快
Which ones in particular were great for you?
你觉得哪一次特别愉快？
Well,you know,about the tongue thing,you know?
就是卷舌头的事
And how I told you about my likes and my dislikes.
还有我告诉你 我喜欢什么，讨厌什么
How I like to melt stuff,and how I dislike stuff that doesn't melt.
我喜欢烧东西 不喜欢不能烧的东西
Right. Okay.
对，好
I feel like I can really talk to you because you're my sister,you know?
我有话都能对你说 因为你是我姐姐
Yeah. I guess I do.
是啊，大概吧
And then I go feel your friend up and make you mad at me.
结果我却摸你朋友 惹你生气
Well,I wasn't hopping mad, you know?
我也没有气到跳脚
You hopped a little bit.
你有跳一、两下
Yeah,I'm really sorry. You know,I'm really....
我真的很抱歉
Okay.
算了
Well,this is my favorite part of the weekend. Right now. This.
我觉得现在这一刻最棒了
This?
现在？
Oh,come on. We went to Times Square.
拜托，我们去了时代广场
We found ninja stars. I almost get my arm broken by a hooker
买到忍者娃娃 我差点被妓女扭断手
She's not a hooker.
她不是妓女
When I tell my friends about her, she will be.
我跟朋友吹嘘时，她就是
On 3!
数到三
1,2
一、二…
Why don't we just go on 2?
为什么不数到二？
Why 2?
为什么？
Because it's faster.
这样比较快
I could've counted to 3 four times without all the "2" talk.
要不是你噜唆，早就数到三了
-All right,but in the future -Heavy thing! Not getting lighter!
好，但是以后… 这个柜子很重，好吗！
1,2
一、二…
So we are going with two?
所以要数到二吗？
A good job,Joe.
乔伊，干得好
Wow.
哇
It's big.
好大
So big it actually makes our doors look smaller.
Maybe my ruler's wrong.
可能是量尺有问题
Maybe all the rulers are wrong.
可能所有的量尺都有问题
It's not that bad. So it blocks a little of your door,a little of mine.
还好嘛，你的挡一点点 我的挡一点点
I got a better idea.
我有更好的主意
How about it blocks none of my door, and a lot of your door?
干脆不要挡我的，都去挡你的
Listen,before I forget, that side is still wet.
先说一声，那边油漆未干
Let me just see if I've got this right.
我跟你确认一下
So this is a half-caf,double-tall, easy hazelnut...
是咖啡因减半、中大杯 少许榛果糖浆
... nonfat,no foam,with whip, extra-hot latte,right?
无脂牛奶、不要奶泡、要打过 要非常烫的拿铁，对吧？
Okay. Great.
太好了
You freak.
变态
Thank you.
谢谢
A coffee to go,please.
一杯咖啡外带
Isabella Rossellini!
是伊莎贝拉罗塞里尼！
Are you serious? Oh,my God!
不会吧？天哪！
Damn! I cannot believe I took her off my list!
该死！我居然把她删掉
Why? Because otherwise you'd go for it?
怎么？不然你会行动吗？
Yeah,maybe.
搞不好
You lie.
骗人
You don't think I'd go up to her?
你不认为我会行动？
It took you 10 years to finally admit you liked me.
你花了十年承认你喜欢我
Yeah? Well,missy,you better be glad that list is laminated.
是吗？你最好庆幸 这份名单已经护贝了
You know what,honey? You go ahead. We'll call her an alternate.
这样吧，你放马过去 就当她是候补人选
Hold my cruller.
好，帮我拿
Are you really gonna let him do this?
你真的要让他去？
He's about to go hit on lsabella Rossellini.
亲爱的，他要去泡 贝拉罗塞里尼耶
I'm just sorry we don't got popcorn.
可惜没有爆米花可吃
I'm Ross.
你好，我是罗斯
You don't know me, but I'm a big,big fan of yours.
你不认识我 但我是你的超级影迷
I mean...
我是说…
...Blue Velvet.
“蓝丝绒”！
I was wondering if I could maybe buy you a cup of coffee.
我能不能请你喝一杯咖啡？
Or reimburse you for that one.
或是把钱给你
Aren't you with that girl over there?
你不是跟那个女生一对？
Well,yeah,kind of.
算是啦
But that's okay. We have an understanding.
但是没关系，我们有共识
We each have this list of five famous people,and you were one of mine.
我们都有一份五个人的名人录 你就在我的名单上
So I'm allowed to sleep with you.
所以我可以跟你上床
It's flattering.
这是恭维
I don't know
还是算了
Wait. Wait,lsabella.
等一下嘛，伊莎贝拉
Don't dismiss this so fast. This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
先别急着否决 这可是千载难逢的机会
Yeah,for you.
对你而言
Is that the list?
这就是名单？
-Yes. -Can I see it?
我可以看吗？
-Come on. -But Okay.
看一下嘛 好吧
I'm not on the list!
我不在名单上
But that's not the final draft.
这不是定案
It's laminated.
都护贝了
Okay,see,you were on my list.
对，好吧，你本来在名单上
But then my friend,Chandler...
但是我的朋友钱德…
... brought up the point that you are international.
指出你太国际化了
So I bumped you for Winona Ryder. Local.
所以我拿薇诺娜瑞德 取代你，比较本土
You know,it's ironic, because I have a list...
真是太讽刺了 因为我也有一份名单
...of five goofy coffeehouse guys.
列了五个咖啡店蠢人
And yesterday,I just bumped you for that guy over there.
就在昨天，那个人取代了你
We're just gonna be friends.
当朋友就好了
You know what?
你知道吗？
Bet you I could fit in there.
我赌我塞得进去
I got five bucks says you can't.
我拿5元赌你塞不进去
Get out your checkbook,mister.
掏支票吧，先生
Oh,I think I have the cash.
我有现金
You are dog,man!
你太逊了
I totally fit!
我塞得刚刚好
Yeah. You got me.
是啊，被你赢了
I'm out five big ones.
我输了5元大钞
There you go.
拿去吧
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh,well,hello,Mr. Lincoln!
总统先生，你好
Better luck next time,buddy!
祝你下次好运
And the drinks are on me!
酒钱由我出